我的支持率上升了95点
and I'm up by 95 points.
压倒性优势[山体滑坡]啊  亲爱滴
We're talking landslide, baby.
泥石流来啦
Here come the mud!
-别闹我了  齐克  -抓住你了
- Okay, don't landslide me, Zeke. - I'm gonna get you.
抓住你了  来啊
I'm gonna get you. Come on, come on.
小吉米  你为什么会想当主席
Why do you even want to be president, Jimmy Jr.?
这样我就可以选舞曲了
To pick songs at dances.
每次都是快歌  慢歌
I hate it when it goes--
不快不慢的歌  我不喜欢
fast song, slow song, medium song.
我想要十首快歌  然后十首慢歌
I want ten fasts, then ten slows.
别说了  哈勃来了
Guys, shh, Haber Danger.
哈勃  你准备好认输了吗
Oh, hey, Habes-- you about ready to say uncle?
还有四天才到竞选日
The election is still four days away.
没听说过龟兔赛跑的故事吗
Ever hear of the tortoise and the hare?
没有
Uh, no.
你是在说小吉米的头发么
What're you sayin' about Jimmy Jr.'s hair?
"兔子"与"头发"同音-他发质可好了  -我是说兔子
- It's nice! - I mean, "Hare," Like, rabbit.
你的头发像黄鼠狼的毛
Well, your hair looks like a weasel.